

Contact

Phone

+91 81034 96299, 79993 82252



Website

https://vishalgoud02.github.io/ personal-profile/



Email

vishalgoud81@gmail.com



Address

Vijay Nagar, Indore (M.P.), India

Languages

English

Conversational/Writing

Hindi

Native

Gujarati

Conversational/Reading

Education

M.B.A. 2015-2017

Aasam Downtown University

B.com 2000-2003

Devi Ahilya University

Certificates

Green Box 2010 Frameboxx, Surat

Post Graduate Deploma in 2005 Multimedia(PGDM)

Xplora Design Skool, Indore

Tools/Softwares

• Figma

• HTML5 + CSS3

Adobe XD

Bootstrap

Illustrator

• SCSS

Photoshop

Tailwind CSS

CorelDraw

JavaScript

Firework

jQuery

Premier

React Basic

After Effect

WordPress

• AI Tools &

Asana

ChatGPT for

• Git (Version

Design & Content

Control)

Vishal Goud

UX UI Designer



Linkedin @vishalkgoud



Behance @vishalgoud



Dribble @vishal_goud

About Me

I'm a Creative UI & UX designer, HTML Developer, and WordPress developer based in Indore (Madhya Pradesh) India. I having 12 years of experience in relevant field.

My expertise lies in conceptualizing and designing engaging software products that are both aesthetically appealing and highly functional. With strong problem-solving abilities and creative skills.

I am able to deliver effective "USER-FRIENDLY DESIGN" solutions that satisfy the needs of both the customer and the end-user.

Experience

Sr. UX UI Designer

Imenso Software, Indore June 2017-Present

As a UI/UX design team lead, I am responsible for supervising the design process and ensuring the creation of visually appealing and user-friendly products for our target audience.

Sr. UX UI Designer

Chapter247 Indore Dec 2016 to May 2017

As a Senior UI/UX Designer, my role involves designing user-friendly interfaces through research, wireframing, and collaborating with other teams to create visually appealing products.

Sr. web faculty

Framebox Indore Sep 2015 till Dec 2016

I train individuals and teams in web design and user interface development, focusing on layout, typography, color theory, and imagery to improve the user experience and website effectiveness.

Sr. Web Designer

MMF Infotech, Indore Aug 2014 till Sep 2015

I design user-friendly interfaces, conduct research, implement frameworks, and collaborate with cross-functional teams to create high-quality digital experiences as a Senior UI/UX Designer.

Sr. UI/UX Designer

Engtelegent BPO Solution, Bhopal Oct 2013 to July 2014

As a Sr. UI/UX Designer, I am responsible for creating visually appealing and userfriendly interfaces, conducting user research, implementing design systems, and collaborating with cross-functional teams to deliver exceptional digital experiences.

Web Designer

WhitePaper, Indore Jan 2013 to Oct 2013

As a web designer, I have extensive experience in creating visually appealing and userfriendly designs for websites, mobile apps.

Web Designer

Webconnect PVT. LTD, Surat Jan 2012 to Dec 2012

As a web Designer, I am responsible for creating visually appealing and user-friendly interfaces, implementing design systems, and collaborating with cross-functional teams to deliver exceptional digital experiences.

Soft Skills

- Design Research
- User Persona
- Design Strategy User Experience (UX Design)
- Adaptive Design
- Interaction Design
- Usability Testing
- Low to High Fidelity Design & **Prototyping**
- Wireframing & Prototyping
- Story Telling & Boarding
- User Interface (UI Design)
- Contextual Research
- up-to-date with UI/UX trends & techni=ology
- Mockups
- Mobile App
- Power BI Screens
- Game Screen
- 2D Animation & Video Editing